#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/avinashgoje (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Python Machine Learning Research

### Languages

Telugu (Limited Working)

Marathi (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

Certifications
CDAC

# Avinash Goje

Data Scientist | Machine Learning Mumbai

## Summary

I am currently working in Myraa technologies, an artificial intelligence company as Technical lead. I was involved in many projects in the company and made hands dirty in various technologies. I have researched on various machine learning algorithms and it helped me a lot in trying out new things.

I was the mentor for one of the groups which were participated in World Biggest Hackathon "Smart India Hackathon" dated on 30 - 31 March 2018.

Before joining this company, I had been through a rigorous training on big data/ data analytics in a famous institute C-DAC.

Now, I am working on the project involving frontend technologies and machine learning, AR. Through this company, I have participated in a hackathon event where we showed a good performance. I love meeting new people and learning new things.

## Experience

Infinx
Data Scientist
October 2019 - Present (11 months)

Xooa Software Engineer July 2019 - October 2019 (4 months) Pune Area, India

Myraa Technologies
2 years 5 months

Machine Learning lead
September 2017 - June 2019 (1 year 10 months)
Navi Mumbai

## Machine learning February 2017 - September 2017 (8 months) Mumbai Area, India

CDAC ACTS, Pune
PG Diploma in Big Data Analytics
February 2016 - August 2016 (7 months)

Pune Area, India

## Education

Swami Ramanand Teerth Marathwada University
Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Electrical, Electronics and Communications
Engineering · (2009 - 2015)

Yeshwant Mahavidyalaya Nanded HSC, Science · (2007 - 2009)